

# Phelisa Nonzwakazi Gqwetha



+27740192226



phelisaggwetha@gmail.com



Cape Town, Western Cape

## Linked in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pheli sa-nonzwakazi-gqwetha-64b1731b b/

# EDUCATION

#### Matric

Matthew Goniwe Memorial High School 2014-2018

## References

Mr Makhosandile, Project codeX - Mentor 067 156 8798,

makhosandile@projectcodex.co

Desiree Hare Praesignis -

Facilitator/Manager 063 703 7380,

desiree.hare@praesignis.com

## PROFILE

Energetic young lady who is determined and willing to learn. Through my experience in working with various volunteer organizations, I developed many skills like communication, listening skills and flexibility. I love working with people. I am always open minded and friendly.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **IT Tech Support**

Praesignis | Cape Town | 06/01/2022 - 23/12/2022

This was a one year program Learnership which was focusing on IT and AWS certification.

- Focus on Troubleshooting, problem solving and more
- Creating websites for projects
- AWS certification with practical labs

#### Software Developer Intern

Project codeX | Cape Town | 16/01/2020 - 23/12/2021

- Focus on the Front-end projects using JavaScript framework React.
- Build a functioning and fully documented application.
- Following Scrum practices to develop the app in a team of 4.

## VOLUNTEER

### **Teacher Assistant**

Action Volunteers Africa (AVA) | Khayelitsha | 28/01/2019 - 2/12/2019

- Assisting foundation phase at Ikhwezi primary school. Tutoring math and english.
- Personal development classes once a week.